Sara L. M. Davis Collection on Tai Lüe Culture
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
Sara L. M. Davis Collection on Tai Lüe Culture 1997-2005
AFC 2006/004
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
5 linear feet (6 boxes) including 17 folders of manuscripts (est. 400 pp.), 25 folders of graphic images (1,166 images), 74 sound recordings, 19 video recordings, and 31 artifacts. Total approximately 1690 items.
Davis, Sara L. M. (Sara Leila Margaret), 1967-
Collection of ethnographic field recordings, photographs, and manuscripts documenting Tai Lüe religious rituals; oral narrative traditions; popular songs; poetry; performances for tourists; interviews with poets and singers; and some local audio and video recordings collected in Sipsongpanna (Xishuangbanna), Yunnan Province, China, by anthropologist Sara L. M. Davis from 1997 to 2005 for her dissertation, published as Song and Silence: Ethnic Revival on China’s Southwest Borders, Columbia University Press, 2005. The collection includes some materials documenting Tai people and traditions in Burma.
Scope and Content
This ethnographic collection is based on the original field work that anthropologist Sara L. M. Davis conducted in Sipsongpanna (Xishuangbanna in Chinese), Yunnan Province, China, and in Kengtung, Shang State, Burma [Myanmar], between 1997 and 2003. The multi-format materials in this collection document Tai Lüe religious rituals, epic oral narratives, popular songs and performances for tourists, as well as interviews with oral poets and popular singers. They consist of her field notes, audio and video recordings, graphic images in the form of photographs and slides, and books published in Yunnan. This research formed the basis of Davis’s book, Song and Silence: Ethnic Revival on China's Southwest Borders (Columbia University Press, 2005). Davis originally traveled to China's southwest borders to conduct doctoral research on ethnic minority folklore, focusing primarily on oral narrative poetry, known as Tai Lüe changkhap or skilled chants. (As used by Davis, changkhap may refer to the genre or to the performers or singers of changkhap.) She was based in the subtropical area of Sipsongpanna in the southwestern region of China, bordering Burma and Laos. Davis lived in Jinghong, the capital of this region, from 1997 to 1998 and made subsequent visits to the area through 2003.
The political challenges of being in a border region of China were immediately evident, and Davis found that many people were initially reluctant to speak openly with her. Instead, she encountered government-sanctioned performances that were marketed primarily to tourists and did not reflect the traditions she had come to document. Davis's field notes offer considerable detail about her experiences staying in monasteries, attending local festivals, and making connections with people in the area. Her search for oral storytellers revealed a growing underground ethnic revival movement. The efforts of young Tai Lüe monks and activists were helping to fuel a resurgence of Tai Lüe Buddhism and an increasing interest in their language and cultural traditions.
The manuscript portion of the collection includes photocopies of Davis's field notes from September 1997 through July 1998; photo, audio, and video logs; song texts in Tai Lüe with some transcriptions into English; articles by Ai No; concert posters (1998); a 2001 calendar, and Davis's book, Song and Silence: Ethnic Revival on China's Southwest Borders (Columbia University Press, 2005). In addition, 47 volumes of publications (1980-2004) were donated with the collection. There are a total of 1,166 graphic images, including 981 3"x5" color photographs, 184 35-mm color slides, and 1 black-and-white photograph, primarily of temples, festivals and ceremonies, and local scenery. Sara Davis took 397 of the color photographs between 1997 and 2001. Wilson Wong took 583 photographs and all 184 of the slides, showing the seventeenth-century temple, Wat Pan Gaew, and the eighth-century temple, Wat Gang, both of which are in Meng Lian. The images are exterior and interior views of the temple, including murals, architectural details, and the living quarters of the monks.
The sound recordings consist of 68 audiocassette tapes, 2 microcassettes, and 2 CDs. They document Tai Lüe religious rituals, epic oral narratives, popular songs, local festivals, and performances for tourists, as well as conference proceedings and interviews with oral poets and popular singers. The majority of the materials are in Tai Lüe, although some are in Chinese and some are in English. Thirty-one of these are Davis's field recordings, two are field recordings by other people, thirty-four are commercially produced, and seven of them are from what is known as the "grey market," tapes that had been previously recorded and were purchased at local markets, but they were not necessarily professionally produced. These recordings include those that were purchased at a stall in the Meng Hun Sunday morning market; those that were purchased at the Tai New Year festivities; and Tai language popular music from Burma, mostly 1970s era; and changkhap, which Davis bought in a Gasa shop in the town center. Many of the commercially produced materials were published by the Yunnan Music Video Publishing House and produced by the literary arts bureau of the TV station; some were produced by the Chinese government, and a number are recordings of Tai Lüe music that were given to Davis by Tai Lüe people in Yunnan.
The moving images are comprised of 12 videocassettes of various sizes and 9 VCDs ["Video Compact Disks" containing moving pictures and sound]. The majority of the videocassettes are Davis's recordings of religious rituals, festivals, and a tourist dance show. There are 8 commercial recordings, and 2 tapes of Davis being interviewed by the staff of the American Folklife Center in 2005. The artifacts in the collection are a bamboo flute with metal reed, woven Tai Lüe cloth, and a bundle of handmade wax candles.
The original notes and headings used by Sara Davis have been transcribed in the finding aid. Researchers should be aware that this finding aid uses both of the English transliteration forms for the region in which Davis conducted her research - Sipsongpanna, the Tai Lüe transliteration into English; and Xishuangbanna, the Chinese transliteration into English. The Library of Congress authority heading is Xishuangbanna, but Davis uses both forms of the transliteration in her field notes and on her folder headings. In her published book, Song and Silence: Ethnic Revival on China's Southwest Borders, she made the editorial decision to use the Tai Lüe transliteration, Sipsongpanna.
Similarly, Tai and Dai, both forms of the English transliteration of the Chinese cultural group, are used in this collection and finding aid. Tai is the Tai language transliteration into English and Dai is the Chinese transliteration into English. The Lü language, the Library of Congress authority heading for the language represented in this collection, is also known as the Lüe language and the Tai Lü language. Davis uses Tai Lüe for both the language and the people.
Biographical History
Sara M. L. Davis earned her Ph.D. at the University of Pennsylvania in East Asian Studies and in Folklore and Folklife. She conducted field research in Xishuangbanna, China in 1997-1998, and has returned several times since then. She has been affiliated with Yale University and University of California, Los Angeles, where she was a visiting scholar, and she was formerly a researcher for Human Rights Watch on China. Davis has contributed to publications including Far Eastern Economic Review, the Wall Street Journal, International Herald Tribune, and Modern China. She is currently the executive director of Asia Catalyst and lives in New York City.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically therein.
People
Davis, Sara L. M. (Sara Leila Margaret), 1967- collector.
Subjects
Buddhist architecture--China--Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou--Photographs.; Buddhist temples--China--Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou--Photographs.; Ethnographic films--China--Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou.; Field recordings--China--Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou.; Lü language--China--Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou.; Oral tradition--China--Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou.; Popular music--China--Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou.; Tai (Southeast Asian people)--Burma--Social life and customs.; Tai (Southeast Asian people)--China--Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou--Poetry.; Tai (Southeast Asian people)--China--Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou--Social life and customs.
Places
Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou (China)--Ethnic relations.; Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou (China)--Folklore.; Xishuangbanna Daizu Zizhizhou (China)--Social life and customs.
Form/Genre
Ethnography.; Interviews.; Photographs.; Sound recordings.; Videocassettes.
Arrangement
The collection has been arranged by format into the following series: Manuscripts, Graphic Images, Sound Recordings, Moving Images, and Artifacts. Davis kept a detailed log of her photographs, sound and video recordings, and her original order has been preserved, although unique AFC ID numbers have been assigned to individual items. She assigned numbers to the photographs she herself took according to a system of "P" followed by a Roman numeral. This numbering system has been used to label each folder of photographs, but individual prints have been labeled using AFC ID numbers (PH0001, PH0002, etc.). Davis also used her own system to label sound recordings, using "AU," followed by sequential letters of the alphabet, and numbers to indicate multiple items within a given series (for example, AU-M1, AU-M2, etc. are a series of narrative legends that were purchased from the television station in Yunnan). While this order has been preserved, AFC has assigned ID numbers, SR01, SR02, etc. Davis used "V" followed by a number to organize moving images; and AFC has retained the numbers but used the preface "MV."
Access
Listening and viewing access to the collection is unrestricted. Physical access to the collection is available at the Folklife Reading Room of the American Folklife Center. Restrictions may apply concerning the use, duplication, or publication of items in this collection. Consult a reference librarian in the Folklife Reading Room for specific information about this collection.
Duplication of the collection materials may be governed by copyright and other restrictions. Please refer to the AFC web site for information on ordering copies of unpublished recordings ( http://www.loc.gov/folklife/recordering.html) and photographic materials ( http://www.loc.gov/folklife/photo_ordering.html).
Acquisition
Sara L. M. Davis donated this collection to the American Folklife Center on February 28, 2006. The collection was initially processed by Sarah Bradley Leighton in the spring of 2006, continued by Judy Ng and Charlotte Cushman in November 2007. The finding aid begun in 2006 has been completed and encoded in 2008 by Nora Yeh.
Related Materials
Davis, Sara L. M., Song and Silence: Ethnic Revival on China's Southwest Borders. New York: Columbia University Press, 2005.
Benjamin Botkin Lecture Series, Song and Silence: Ethnic Revival on China's Southwest Borders, lecture by Sara L. M. Davis (AFC 2005/041) December 13, 2005.
Collection Concordance by Format
Manuscript Materials
17 folders AFC Boxes 1&2
Graphic Images
981 3x5 color photographs AFC Boxes 2&3
184 35 mm color slides AFC Box 3
1 black-and-white photograph AFC Box 2
Sound Recordings
68 audiocassettes AFC Boxes 4&5
2 microcassettes AFC Boxes 4&5
2 CDs AFC Box 5
Moving Images
9 Hi-8 videocassettes, color, sound AFC Box 5
2 Mini-DV videocassettes, color, sound AFC Box 5
1 VHS videocassette, color, sound AFC Box 5
9 VCDs, color, sound AFC Box 5
Artifacts
1 flute AFC AR01, Box 6
1 Tai Lüe textile AFC AR02, Box 6
29 handmade wax candles AFC AR03, Box 6
http://lccn.loc.gov/2008700350
Collection Inventory
- Manuscripts
  - Finding Aid for this collection. (Box 1, Folder 01)
  - Field Notes I. September 1997 - November 20, 1997. (Box 1, Folder 02)
    Photocopy of the first field notebook kept by Sara Davis. 160 pages.
  - Field Notes II. December 1997 - February 21, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 03)
    Photocopy of the second field notebook kept by Sara Davis. 169 pages.
  - Field Notes III. February 21, 1998 - April 1998. (Box 1, Folder 04)
    Photocopy of the third field notebook kept by Sara Davis. 239 pages.
  - Field Notes IV. May 1998 - July 1998. (Box 1, Folder 05)
    Photocopy of the fourth field notebook kept by Sara Davis. 197 pages.
  - Photograph, Video, Audio Logs. September 1997 - July 1998. (Box 1, Folder 06)
    Photocopy of the logs kept by Sara Davis to record the contents, date, and location of field photographs, and collected videos and audio recordings. 96 pages.
  - Song text - Aye (Bo) Saut. "Dharma in ten lives." Undated. (Box 1, Folder 07)
    Song text written in Tai Lüe with English notes and translations. 11 pages.
  - Song Text - Aye (Bo) Saut. "Man's explanation of city-state." Undated. (Box 1, Folder 08)
  - Transcribed song lyrics - Khanan Zhuai. "Praise for prince." Undated. (Box 1, Folder 09)
    Transcribed song lyrics written in Tai Lüe with English notes and translations. 4 pages.
  - Transcribed song lyrics - Sithat Auk Boht. From 1998 recording. Undated. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Transcribed song lyrics written in Tai Lüe with English notes and translations. 28 pages.
  - Articles - Ai No. Circa 1997-1998. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Photocopies of articles written in Chinese and Tai Lüe by author, Ai No, expert on Tai Lüe culture and folklore. 186 pages.
  - Concert Posters - Sai Sang Mao, Xishaungbanna, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Advertising a concert in Xishaungbanna of Sai Sang Mao, a famous Burmese Tai performer. 7 pages.
  - Calendar by Wat Pajay in Sipsongbanna, 2001. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Monthly flip calendar for the year 2001 printed in Chinese and Tai Lüe with photographs. 7 pages.
  - Davis, Sara L. M. Song and Silence: Ethnic Revival on China's Southwest Borders. New York: Columbia University Press, 2005. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    200 pages.
  - Flyers from Sara L. M. Davis Benjamin Botkin Lecture. December 13, 2005. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    3 pages.
  - Photocopies of covers, title pages, and copyright information page of published material with Chinese translation. 1980-2001. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Item No. 1 - Item No. 20.
    Published material is printed in Chinese and Tai Lüe with some English translations. 63 pages.
  - Photocopies of covers, title pages, and copyright information page of published material with Chinese translation. 1988-2004. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Item No. 21 - Item No. 47.
    Published material is printed in Chinese and Tai Lüe with some English translations. 72 pages.
- Graphic Images
  [NOTE: Photographs in the PIII, PVII, and PXIII series are not included by donor.]
  - PH0001-PH0076: PI. November 1997. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Monk initiation ceremony in Da Menglong, Xishuangbanna.
    76 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
  - PH0077-PH0084: PII. October 1997. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Minority Atmosphere Park.
    8 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
    [NOTE: Photographs in the PIII series are not included by donor.]
  - PH0085-PH0102: PIV. December 1997. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Jinghong, general.
    18 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
  - PH0103-PH0129: PV. January 1998. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Dai wedding, Dai Singer, Festival, Buddhist parade.
    27 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
  - PH0130-PH0136: PVI. February 1998. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Moonshine still near Ganlanba and monk initiation.
    7 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
    [NOTE: Photographs in the PVII series are not included by donor.]
  - PH0137-PH0186: PVIII. February 10, 1998 - February 11, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Khu ba ceremony in Da Menglong, Xishuangbanna.
    50 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
  - PH0187-PH0259: PIX. March 1998. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Temples in Meng Zhe, Xishaungbanna.
    73 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
  - PH0260-PH0307: PX. March 11, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Temples in Meng Lian.
    48 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
  - PH0308-PH0318: PXI. March 14, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Young singers in Ganlanda/Meng Ham, Xishuangbanna.
    11 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
  - PH0319-PH0332: PXII. April 14, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Dragon boat races and song texts.
    14 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
    [NOTE: Photographs in the PXIII series are not included by donor.]
  - PH0333-PH0358: PXIV. January 1999. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Kunming Nationalities Theme Park.
    26 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
  - PH0359-PH0368: PXV. June 1998. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Construction of Jinghong superhighway.
    10 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
  - PH0369-PH0404. June 2001. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Tourism and hotel construction.
    36 color prints. Photographer: Sara L. M. Davis.
    [NOTE: These photographs were not assigned a roman numeral within the previous series.]
  - PH0405-PH0409. Former palace of Tai Lüe prince of Kengtung, Burma. Circa 2001. Sara Davis with a singer. June 1998. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    4 color prints. 1 black-and-white photograph.
  - PH0410-PH0489. Seventeenth-century temple, Wat Pan Gaew in Meng Lian, Sipsongpanna. (1 of 2). March 1998. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    People, exterior, architectural details of roof, doors, windows.
    80 color prints. Photographer: Wilson Wong.
  - PH0490-PH0564. Seventeenth-century temple, Wat Pan Gaew in Meng Lian, Sipsongpanna. (2 of 2). March 1998. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Exterior windows and walls (writing and parts of murals). Interior pillars, ceiling, writing on wall, kitchen, drums.
    75 color prints. Photographer: Wilson Wong
  - PH0565-PH0672. Eighth-century temple, Wat Gang in Meng Lian, Sipsongpanna. (1 of 3). March 1998. (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Exterior architectural details of roof, doors, windows. Interior pillars, ceiling, area for worship.
    108 color prints. Photographer: Wilson Wong.
  - PH0673-PH0776. Eighth-century temple, Wat Gang in Meng Lian, Sipsongpanna. (2 of 3). March 1998. (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Exterior pillars and murals.
    104 color prints. Photographer: Wilson Wong.
  - PH0777-PH0872. Eighth-century temple, Wat Gang in Meng Lian, Sipsongpanna. (3 of 3). March 1998. (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Exterior murals and living quarters.
    96 color prints. Photographer: Wilson Wong.
  - PH0873-PH0936. Eighth-century temple, Wat Gang in Meng Lian, Sipsongpanna. (1 of 2). March 1998. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Exterior of buildings, murals, doors. Interior ceilings and pillars.
    64 color prints. Photographer: Wilson Wong.
  - PH0937-PH0992. Eighth-century temple, Wat Gang in Meng Lian, Sipsongpanna. (2 of 2). March 1998. (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Living quarters and monks.
    56 color prints. Photographer: Wilson Wong.
  - PH0993-PH1030. Eighth-century temple, Wat Gang in Meng Lian, Sipsongpanna. March 1998. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Exterior of buildings, roofs, doors, stone carvings.
    38 color slides. Photographer: Wilson Wong.
  - PH1031-PH1068. Eighth-century temple, Wat Gang in Meng Lian, Sipsongpanna. March 1998. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Murals.
  - PH1069-PH1166. Eighth-century temple, Wat Gang in Meng Lian, Sipsongpanna. March 1998. (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Exterior of buildings, murals, windows, doors, ceilings, pillars, stone carving.
    98 color slides. Photographer: Wilson Wong.
  - Photo documentation accompanying MV 09. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Photo documentation of artifacts. (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Sound Recordings
  [NOTE: No AU-I or AU-V assigned by donor.]
  - AU-A Yi Guang's Home. October 1997. (Box 4, Sr 01)
    Singing, flute.
    60-minute audiocassette tape field recording.
  - AU-B Da Menglong Monk Initiation Parties. November 1997. (Box 4, Sr 02)
    Performed in homes of young boys undergoing initiation as monks.
  - AU-C Gasa, Sipsongpanna. January 1998. (Box 4, Sr 03)
    Interview and song with Khana Zhuai, Sipsongpanna's most famous singer. (Recorded outside, several translators interpreting. Humming from recorder.)
  - AU-D Wat Ba Jie, Jinghong. Temple Tai-language popular music festival, 9-10pm. January 1998. (Box 4, Sr 04)
    "New Star" is backup band.
  - AU-E Continuation of above, 10-11pm. January 1998. (Box 4, Sr 05)
  - AU-F Continuation of above, 11-12 pm. January 1998. (Box 4, Sr 06)
  - AU-G Continuation of above, 2nd day, afternoon. January 1998. (Box 4, Sr 07)
  - AU-H Continuation of above, 2nd day, 9-10 pm. January 1998. (Box 4, Sr 08)
    [NOTE: No AU-I assigned by donor.]
  - AU-J Continuation of above, 2nd day, 10-11 pm. January 1998. (Box 4, Sr 09)
  - AU-K Da Menglong, Sipsongpanna. (1 of 2). February 1998. (Box 4, Sr 10)
    Performance by Changkhap.
    Competition of two singers on occasion of six monks' ascension to "khu ba" status; performed on temple grounds
  - AU-L Da Menglong, Sipsongpanna - continuation. (2 of 2). February 1998. (Box 4, Sr 11)
  - AU-M1. Sung by Ai Gaen, Yi Awn, narrative legend (1 of 2). Undated. (Box 4, Sr 12)
    Produced by the literary arts bureau of Sipsongpanna People's Broadcasting Corporation.
    60-minute audiocassette tape commercial recording.
  - AU-M2. Sung by Ai Gaen, Yi Awn, narrative legend (2 of 2). Undated. (Box 4, Sr 13)
  - AU-M3. Undated. (Box 4, Sr 14)
    Series Title: Minzu Yishu Zhi Hua: Minge. [Flowers of Ethnic Arts: Folksongs] Tai Zu Minge [Tai Ethnic Folksongs].
    "Sithat Auk Boht" sung by Yi Guang, Ai Khang Yay - narrative legend.
  - AU-M4. Undated. (Box 4, Sr 15)
    "Wei Sian Tala." Sung by Yi Guang, Ai Sang, and Ai Gaew - narrative legend.
  - AU-M5. "Nang Gin Bu." - narrative legend (1 of 2). Undated. (Box 4, Sr 16)
  - AU-M6. "Nang Gin Bu." - narrative legend (2 of 2). Undated. (Box 4, Sr 17)
  - AU-M7 "Nang Gin Bu." Sung by Ai Kham Lust, Yi Guang Nuoy, Yi Diew (1 of 2). Undated. (Box 4, Sr 18)
  - AU-M8 "Nang Gin Bu." Sung by Ai Kham Lust, Yi Guang Nuoy, Yi Diew (2 of 2). Undated. (Box 4, Sr 19)
  - AU-M9 Duet-duels. A: Sung by Yi Awn, Ai Kham Yay. B: Sung by Yi Guang Nuoy, Yi Diew. Undated. (Box 4, Sr 20)
  - AU-M10 Housewarming Songs sung by Yi Guang Nuoy, Ai Khang Yay (1 of 2). Undated. (Box 4, Sr 21)
  - AU-M11 Housewarming Songs sung by Yi Guang Nuoy, Ai Khang Yay (2 of 2). Undated. (Box 4, Sr 22)
  - AU-M12 "Zhet Da Pa" sung by Yi Guang, Ai Khang Yay. Undated. (Box 4, Sr 23)
  - AU-M13 "Ew Da Ho" sung by Ai Kham Lust, Yi Guang. Undated. (Box 4, Sr 24)
  - AU-M14 "Pam Tai" sung by Ai Khang Yay, Yi Guang. Undated. (Box 4, Sr 25)
  - AU-M15 "Sipsawug Lai Sii" sung by Ai Khang Yay, Yi Guang. Undated. (Box 4, Sr 26)
    60-minute audiocassette recording.
  - AU-M16 "Ga Peut" sung by Ai Kham Lust, Yi Guang. Undated. (Box 4, Sr 27)
  - AU-N Music by Ai Sam with New Star Band; lyrics by Ai Han Liang. Undated. (Box 4, Sr 28)
    Recorded in Burma, for Yunnan Audio Visual Production, Co. in cooperation with Wat Ba Jie.
  - AU-O Bo Saut (flute and singer); Ai Neun Ew (singer); Yi Euy Siang (singer); Yi Siang (singer). March 1998. (Box 4, Sr 29)
    Recorded in Ganlanha, Yunnan.
  - AU-P1 Meng Zhe (singer with guitar). Undated. (Box 4, Sr 30)
    Purchased at a stall in the Meng Hun Sunday morning market.
  - AU-P2 Burmese singer with Tai guitar. Undated. (Box 4, Sr 31)